<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Growth Checker</string>
    <string name="slide1text">Get over every addiction</string>
    <string name="slidetext2">Track your growth</string>
    <string name="slidetext3">Partake in challenges </string>
    <string name="AdUnit">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="slidetext4">Receive encouragement awards</string>
    <string name="slide1desc">What addictions have you struggled with over
the years.  You can free yourself now.</string>
    <string name="slidetext2desc">Track your growth using tables and plotted
graphs.</string>
    <string name="slidetext3desc">Engage in many challenges ranging from 2 to
several weeks to break out of addictions. </string>
    <string name="slidetext4desc">Get awarded for every concluded challenge.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="summary">Addictions can sometimes be very hard to break. Often times breaking them alone always prove abortive. Hence, there is every need for help and support either from
trusted people or useful materials.
We find it hard to communicate what we
are going through with others due to certain reasons
which mostly could be the fear of being ridiculed.  Well,
this was thought through and the Growth checker
app was developed for this reason and others.
When dealing with addictions, a better sense of accountability
 helps to better deal with the situation. This summarizes what this
app is all about. Days of involvement in the addiction in question
lead to subtraction of very high points and days of non involvement
plus doing certain activities which will help with growth leads to
the addition of positive points. All these are plotted on graphs for
better visualization of growth on a daily basis.
The essence of this app is to serve as a companion throughout
the breaking free period. </string>
    <string name="d1">Decide to Change:</string>
    <string name="d2">The decision to change is one of the most important steps in overcoming an addiction. By acknowledging that a change is needed, it means that you recognize that there is a problem and have a desire to address it. Making the decision to change and deciding what that will look like is a process that often takes time. This is known as the contemplation stage because it involves thinking about whether to change and how.  Ambitious goals are not always best, however. It is better to set a goal that you will actually achieve than to plan to quit "cold turkey" and end up relapsing, which can be more dangerous than simply continuing without any changes.Consulting a doctor, addiction counselor, or psychologist is particularly helpful at this stage as they can help you understand the risks and what can help alleviate them.</string>
    <string name="d3">Prepare to Change:</string>
    <string name="d4">Once you are clear on your goal, you may still need to prepare to change. Preparations include removing addictive substances from your home as well as eliminating triggers in your life that may make you more likely to use those substances again.This often means getting rid of paraphernalia or other items that might trigger your desire to use a substance or engage in a harmful behavior. You may also find it necessary to change your routine so that you have less contact with people or settings that trigger cravings.  Other ways to prepare include deciding what approach you plan to use to overcome your addiction and getting the resources that you need to be successful. \nFor example, a person who is trying to quit smoking would start by deciding whether they are going to stop smoking cold turkey or gradually reduce their nicotine use. Next, they would get the tools they need to quit successfully such as finding a support group, buying nicotine replacement therapy (NRT) products, or talking to a healthcare provider about prescription smoking cessation medications.</string>
    <string name="d5">Reach Out to Healthcare Providers:</string>
    <string name="d6">For alcohol and drug addictions, it is a good idea to talk to a doctor or local drug clinic about whether you need medical help in quitting. There are options for medications to help alleviate withdrawal symptoms. In some cases, you may need medical supervision during the detox process.  If you have an underlying mental health problem, such as anxiety or depression, it could worsen during the withdrawal phase. Healthcare providers can be very supportive and helpful while navigating these challenges.</string>

    <string name="aboutus">We are a tech firm concerned with creating value with our products.  The mission is to make readily available apps to help in several phases of development of a persons life.  Educational apps, personal development apps and others. This is our own way of being involved in everyones growth with the values we create with our products.</string>
</resources>